A Guide to the Notar Public Applications, 1906-1910
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Notary Public Applications, 1906-1910
The Library of Virginia
39502
.45 cu. ft. (1 box)
Secretary of the Commonwealth
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
No acquisition is available.
Scope and Content
This collection documents applications to be commissioned as Notary Publics for their respective county or city of residence. Records include correspondence, and the applications detail the name of the individual, place of residence, the signature of Governor Claude Swanson and the date of approval.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically, and records are arranged alphabetically by last name.
Contents List
- Notary Public Applications, 1906-1910., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
  - A-K, 1906. (Folder 1)
    - Allen, E.B.
    - Allison, Annie M.
    - Bagley, C.S.
    - Bolter, L.E.
    - Broche, William C.
    - Carter, Oscar
    - Davidson, B.M.
    - Davis, Paul.
    - Gerke, Fred E.
    - Grigsby, W.C.
    - Hancock, M.V.
    - Hanson, Murray
    - Hatch, T.J.
    - Holt, Virginius P.
    - Hudgins, Mayme
    - Hudson, Raymond
    - Hudson, T.E.
    - Jackson, Ira
    - Kent, J.A.
  - L-W, 1906. (Folder 2)
    - Leake, Walter A.
    - Lewis, M.C.
    - Little, H.W.
    - Martin, Samuel
    - Mays, Grace
    - McNichols, James E.
    - Meade, J.H.
    - Miller, J.C.
    - Page, C.C.
    - Pearson, Harry L.
    - Robinette, Charles J.
    - Shrader, I. Terrell
    - Snow, J.F.
    - Taliaferro, H.T.
    - Tarshis, Herman
    - Tinsley, W.F.
    - Tustall, Anna
    - Whittle, Staffod
  - A-L, 1907. (Folder 3)
    - Armstrong, H.D.
    - Boyenton, W.H.
    - Bradshaw, H.T.
    - Burnett, H.P.
    - Cary, M.D.
    - Coleman, R.T.
    - Cooper, Edward
    - Downing, J.A.
    - Fairnholt, E.B.
    - Gibbs, William J.
    - Haney, S.E.
    - Hart, Amy C.
    - Hurst, Sam
    - Irby, H.H.
    - Joyner, J.F.
    - Leigh, J.H.
    - Loving, H.C.
  - P-Y, 1907. (Folder 4)
    - Parker, J.
    - Payne, James W.
    - Peyton, Robert E.
    - Phillips, H.J.
    - Plummer, E.H.
    - Price, T.
    - Pulley, John J.
    - Rhudy, W.W.
    - Robertson, A.F.
    - Robinson, John H.
    - Sanders, W.B.
    - Snapp, W.A.
    - Turner, John A.
    - Vaughn, W.E.S.
    - Westbrook, Lillian
    - Yeary, Oscar
  - A-J, 1908. (Folder 5)
    - Atkinson, W.E.
    - Barnstead, S.G.
    - Blevins, Granville L.
    - Bremner, George
    - Brooking, Keesee
    - Derring, J.A.
    - Dulaney, Paul
    - Elan, Thomas
    - Gaines, Robert M.
    - Gentry, John L.
    - Godsey, James
    - Graham, Robert M.
    - Greer, J.C.
    - Harris, S.C.
    - Haynes, W.T.
    - Hays, T.W.
    - Hilten, James
    - Hutchinson, Thomas B.
    - James, Harry N.
    - Jenkins, Effie
    - Johnson, A. Page
  - K-Y, 1908. (Folder 6)
    - Kline, G.D.
    - Lewis, J.L.
    - Marks, John Henry
    - Marshall, J.W.
    - Martin, J.W.
    - Mayo, G.H.I.
    - McRae, R.S.
    - Miley, W.B.
    - Mooring, W.P.
    - Norman, J.M.
    - Pettus, W.S.
    - Robins, H. Copeland
    - Sandridge, C.E.
    - Sexson, W.M.
    - Shackleton, J.A.
    - Taylor, H.A.
    - Trimble, Rebecca
    - Umberger, C.E.
    - Williams, A.B.
    - Wise, E.S.
    - Youngblood, I.E.
  - A-L, 1909. (Folder 7)
    - Abernathy, J.W.
    - Bagley, Thomas
    - Barksdale, Herbert
    - Boyd, F.F.
    - Carter, Clyde
    - Cole, G.W.
    - Daniel, John N.
    - Franklin, W.C.
    - Gemmel, A.M.
    - Hamilton, Hugh
    - Jackson, H.G.
    - Jones, W.C.
    - Love, J. Hunter
  - M-W, 1909. (Folder 8)
    - Martin, T.J.
    - McKenna, J.T.
    - Metzger, John B.
    - Moore, Ola M.
    - Morgan, J.R.
    - Palmer, Barton
    - Price, Edna
    - Ratliff, M.B.
    - Ricketts, E.B.
    - Ross, T.W.
    - Schweickert, O.L.
    - Shacklette, W.S.
    - Smith, Ernest E.
    - Sutton, Nicholas M.
    - Wall, J.W.
    - Warren, T.S.
  - M, W, 1910. (Folder 9)
    - Moore, Thomas
    - Welsh, John